http://www.bookcost.com/privacy.php

Effective on February 1, 2010
This privacy statement describes how Direct Textbooks collects and uses the personal information you provide on our Web site: directtextbook.com.
It also describes the choices available to you regarding our use of your personal information and how you can access and update this
information.
Collection and Use of Personal Information
We collect the following personal information from you
Preferences Information such as product wish lists, order history, marketing preferences
As is true of most Web sites, we automatically gather information about your computer such as your IP address, browser type,
referring/exit pages, and operating system.
We use this information to
Improve our Web site and marketing efforts
Information Sharing
We will share your personal information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy statement. We do not sell
your personal information to third parties.
We may also disclose your personal information
as required by law such as to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal process
when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others,
investigate fraud, or respond to a government request,
if Direct Textbooks is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email
and/or a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices
you may have regarding your personal information,
to any other third party with your prior consent to do so.
Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies
We may use cookies, for example, to keep track of your preferences and profile information. Cookies are also used to collect general
usage and volume statistical information that does not include personal information.
Web beacons
Our Web pages contain electronic images known as Web beacons (sometimes called single-pixel gifs) and are used along with cookies
to compile aggregated statistics to analyze how our site is used and may be used
in some of our emails to let us know which emails and links have been opened by recipients. This allows us to gauge the
effectiveness of our customer communications and marketing campaigns.
Our Web pages may also contain electronic images known as Web beacons (sometimes called single-pixel gifs) that are set by our
third party partners.
Web beacons are used along with cookies enabling our partners to compile aggregated statistics to analyze how our site is
used.
We use a third party to gather information about how you and others use our Web site.
For example, we will know how many users access a specific page and which links they clicked on. We use this aggregated information
to understand and optimize how our site is used.
Links to Other Web Sites
Our Site includes links to other Web sites whose privacy practices may differ from those of Direct Textbooks.
If you submit personal information to any of those sites, your information is governed by their privacy statements. We encourage you
to carefully read the privacy statement of any Web site you visit.
Security
The security of your personal information is important to us. We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the
personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it.
No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, we cannot
guarantee its absolute security.
We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services.
If you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services contact us at service@directtextbook.com.
We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.
If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can contact us at service@directtextbook.com
Additional Policy Information
Our Web site includes Widgets, which are interactive mini-programs that run on our site to provide specific services from another
company (e.g. displaying the news, opinions, music, etc).
Personal information, such as your email address, may be collected through the Widget. Cookies may also be set by the Widget to
enable it to function properly. Information collected by this Widget is governed
by the privacy policy of the company that created it.
Links to Other Web Sites
Our Site includes links to other Web sites whose privacy practices may differ from those of Direct Textbooks.
If you submit personal information to any of those sites, your information is governed by their privacy statements.
We encourage you to carefully read the privacy statement of any Web site you visit.
Correcting and Updating Your Personal Information
To review and update your personal information to ensure it is accurate, contact us at service@directtextbook.com
.
Notification of Privacy Statement Changes
We may update this privacy statement to reflect changes to our information practices.
If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a
notice on this Site prior to the change becoming effective.
We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.
Contact Information
You can contact us about this privacy statement by writing or email us at the address below:
We love to help. Questions? Suggestions? Let us know.
Send Message
Or get instant answers in our FAQs:
• How to Sell Textbooks
• Buying Used Textbooks
• Rent Textbooks
• Buying Online eBooks
Loading...
Close
